globalinformationnetwork.com 2011-08-20

# The Global Information Network

This Privacy Policy explains how this site treats “personal information.” “Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like a name, address, e-mail address, social security number or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This site is owned and operated by Global Information Network FDN (“GIN”) for your personal use and information. By accessing and browsing this site, you are accepting, and are bound by, this Privacy Policy. As used herein, GIN shall include Global Information Network FDN, its affiliates and related companies, and each of their subscribers, agents, directors, officers, employees and assigns. 

**Categories of Personal Information Collected**

GIN receives and collects the following categories of personal information.

  * Information that you provide: we may collect information provided by visitors to the site, such as the names and e-mail addresses of those who submit membership or affiliate applications, or who communicate with us via e-mail or through an online contact form, as well as information submitted through online ordering and by signing up for our mailings.
  * Information collected by our Web servers: when you visit this site, our Web servers may automatically collect your “internet protocol” (IP) address and information about the web page that you visited immediately prior to visiting our site.
  * Cookies: a cookie is a small text file that is sent to your Web browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit this site, a cookie may be sent to your computer. You can control whether or not you want to accept cookies by adjusting the settings of your browser. 

**Use of Personal Information Collected**

GIN may use the information that visitors provide us to improve the content of our site, to inform visitors of new products and services, information and for other developmental, operational, or commercial purposes, and to transmit the personal information to third parties for the same reasons. 

GIN may use the information collected by our Web servers to help us track our visitors use of the site, analyze traffic patterns, and identify sources of web traffic to our site.

GIN may use cookies to record session information, such as items that visitors add to their online shopping cart. 

GIN may also use the information we collect to investigate, prevent or take action against suspected illegal activities. We may use the information for legal proceedings, such as responding to subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. In the event that our company or its assets are acquired by or merged with a third party, the information collected by our site may be one of the assets transferred. 

GIN reserves the right to share your personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your email address, postal address, and telephone number with its affiliates and third parties.

**Sites not covered by this Policy**

This Policy does not apply to websites that this site links to, websites that link to this site, websites framed by this site, or any other third party websites. GIN is not responsible for the content, products or services on those sites. You should visit those third-party websites to determine the privacy policy and terms of use that govern those sites.

**Security Measures**

Our web hosting company uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer information exchanged with our site. Our web hosting company has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Although we believe that our web hosting company provides appropriate security measures, we are not responsible for the practices, actions or inactions of that company. 

**Changes to this Policy**

GIN reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and without advanced warning, by updating this page. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore review this Privacy Policy every time you visit this site. 

**Terms of Use/Membership Agreement**

Nothing herein waives, limits or in any way modifies ourTerms of Use or the Membership Agreement. 

**“Opt Out Rights”**

If, at any time after visiting the site, you change your mind about receiving information from the site or sharing your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, you may request an opt out. 

**Questions or Additional Information**

If you have any questions about this Policy, or if you would like additional information, please do not hesitate to contact us. 

Last Updated: June 11, 2009 

We are an informational organization. We are a "member sharing with other members" private association. We do not provide financial planning, tax, legal, investment, or medical advice. Consultation with independent expert advisors is strongly recommended. We are not a business opportunity.
